Guide to the Mandy Carter Papers, 1970-2013 RL.00195
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Gigs and Events Series, 1979-2013, 108 boxes
  - Old Speaking Gigs to File, 1994-1995, 4 folders (Box 219)
  - Gigs, 1994-2001 (Box 219)
  - Gigs, 1995, 3 folders (Box 219)
  - Interviews, Print/TV/Radio, 1995 (Box 219)
  - Speaking Requests, 1995-1996 (Box 219)
  - Gigs, 1995-1996 (Box 219)
  - Old Gigs, 1996 (Box 219)
  - Gigs, 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box 220)
  - Duke, 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box 220)
  - UNC-Chapel Hill, 1997 (Box 220)
  - Gigs, 1998, 3 folders (Box 220)
  - Gigs, 1997-1998 (Box 220)
  - Speeches, 2001-2007 (Box 220)
  - Media, 2003 (Box 220)
  - Gigs, 2003 (Box 220)
  - Gigs, 2004, 2 folders (Box 220)
  - Gigs, 2005 (Box 220)
  - Gay Freedom Day Parade and Celebration, Float Applications, San Francisco, Calif., 1979 (Box 112)
  - Gay Parade, San Francisco, Calif., 1979-1982 (Box 112)
  - Gay Olympics, San Francisco, Calif., 1982 Aug. 28-Sept. 25 (Box 112)
  - North Carolina Gay and Lesbian Conference, UNC-Chapel Hill, Chapel Hill, N.C., 1983 Mar. 25-27 (Box 112)
  - Civil Disobedience Actions, Washington, D.C., 1987 (Box 112)
  - Aids in Black Community NC Conference, N.C. Central University, Durham, N.C., 1987 Feb. 21 (Box 112)
  - Pride '87, Raleigh, Durham, Chapel Hill, N.C., 1987 June 27 (Box 112)
  - National March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights, Washington, D.C., 1987 Oct. 11 and 1988 Oct. 6-11 (Box 113)
  - Southern March on DC List, Washington, D.C. (Box 113)
  - Busses, Raleigh, Durham, Chapel Hill, N.C., 1987 Oct. 11 (Box 113)
  - Ladyslipper Board Meeting Minutes, 1988 Jan. 20 (Box 113)
  - National Black Gay & Lesbian Conference, Los Angeles, Calif., 1988 Feb. 12-14 (Box 113)
  - KKK Response Activism, Durham, N.C., 1988 June 13 (Box 113)
  - NC Pride '88, Raleigh, N.C., 1988 June 25, 4 folders (Box 113)
  - Gay Games, 1988 July 2-4 (Box 113)
  - NC Now State Conference, Durham, N.C., 1988 Oct. 1 (Box 103)
  - National Coming Out Day, 1988 Oct. 11 (Box 113)
  - Gay Lesbian Vote '88, Fall 1988 (Box 114)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, Creating Change Conference, Washington, D.C., 1988 Nov. 18-20 (Box 104)
  - Lobby Workshop NCCGLE, 1989 Jan. 14 (Box 114)
  - Ladyslipper Board Meeting, Durham, N.C., 1989 Jan. (Box 114)
  - National Black Gay & Lesbian Conference, 1989 Feb. 17-20 (Box 114)
  - Combating Homophobia Workshop, 1989 Mar. 28 (Box 114)
  - Southeastern Conference for Lesbians & Gay Men XIV, Dallas, Tex., 1989 Apr. 13-16, 2 folders (Box 114)
  - Pride '89, Raleigh, N.C., 1989 June 24, 4 folders (Box 114)
  - Stonewall 20: San Francisco Lesbian/Gay Freedom Day Parade and Celebration, San Francisco, Calif., 1989 June 25 (Box 114)
  - ASO Retreat, 1989 Sept. 9 (Box 114)
  - AHEC Gig Greensboro, Winston-Salem, N.C., 1989 Nov. 9 (Box 115)
  - Ladyslipper Board Meeting, 1990 Jan. 30 (Box 115)
  - Executives Retreat, Laguna, Calif., 1990 Feb 22-25 (Box 115)
  - Southeastern Conference for Lesbians and Gay Men, Raleigh, N.C., 1990 Mar. 22-25 (Box 115)
  - Civil Disobedience Actions at White House, Washington, D.C., 1990 Mar. 24 (Box 115)
  - NARAL-N.C. Lobbying Workshop, 1990 May 15 (Box 115)
  - Southern Women's Music Festival, 1990 May 24-28 (Box 115)
  - AIDs in the 1990s State-of-the-State Conference, N.C., 1990 June (Box 115)
  - South Carolina Pride March, 1990 June 23 (Box 115)
  - Pride '90, Chapel Hill/Carrboro, N.C., 1990 June 30, 9 folders (Box 115-116)
  - Gay Games III, Team No. Carolina, 1990 Aug. 4-11 (Box 116)
  - NCHRF Board Meeting, 1990 Aug. 18 (Box 116)
  - 1990 National Coming Out Day, 1990 Oct. 11 (Box 116)
  - AWMAC Retreat, Berkeley, Calif., 1990 Oct. 26-28 (Box 116)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, Creating Change Conference, Minneapolis-St. Paul, Minn., 1990 Nov. 10-12 (Box 104)
  - NELGSA Conference, Williamsburg, Va., 1991 Mar. 1-4 (Box 116)
  - Private Money in Public Elections, Legislative and Electoral Consequences, 1991 May 10-11 (Box 116)
  - South Carolina Pride, Columbia, S.C., 1991 June 22 (Box 117)
  - Pride '91, Durham, N.C., 1991 June 29 (Box 117)
  - SECLGM Conference, Baltimore, Md., 1991 July 4-7 (Box 117)
  - Pride '91, Richmond, Va., 1991 Sept. 8 (Box 117)
  - NC Now Leadership Retreat, Wilmington, N.C., 1991 Nov 1-3 (Box 103)
  - Ladyslipper Board Meeting Minutes, 1992 Jan. 27 (Box 117)
  - Non-Violent Civil Disobedience Training, 1992 Feb. 23 (Box 117)
  - NWPC/CHWPC Campaign Skills Training for Women, 1992 June 20 (Box 117)
  - DC Coalition of Black Lesbians & Gay Men, 1992 July 31-Aug. 2 (Box 117)
  - 17th Annual Organizer Training Program (WRL), 1992 Aug. 7-16 (Box 117)
  - AIDS Watch, Washington, D.C., 1992 Sept. 8-9 (Box 118)
  - International Conference of Lesbian and Gay Officials, 1992 Nov. 20-22 (Box 118)
  - North Carolina Lesbian/Gay History Project Organizational Meeting, 1993 Jan. 17 (Box 118)
  - Gay and Lesbian Inaugural Celebration, Washington, D.C., 1993 Jan. 18-20 (Box 118)
  - Sixth National Black Gay and Lesbian Conference, Long Beach, Calif., 1993 Feb. 11-15 (Box 118)
  - Leadership Conference, Washington, D.C., 1993 Apr. 22-25 (Box 118)
  - March on Washington for LGB Equal Rights and Liberation, 1993 Apr. 25, 4 folders (Box 118)
  - Fight Right Retreat, Blue Mounain Center, N.Y., 1993 Apr. 30-May 2 (Box 119)
  - Black Pride '93, Washington, D.C., 1993 May 28-30 (Box 119)
  - Rebuild America II, Washington, D.C., 1993 June 10-12 (Box 119)
  - Congressional Black Caucus Foundation's 23rd Annual Legislative Weekend, Washington, D.C., 1993 Sept. 15-19 (Box 119)
  - Russia Training Project Events, circa 1994 (Box 119)
  - Defending the Family, Strategies for Economic Justice and Hope, Washington, D.C., 1994 Jan. 5-7, 2 folders (Box 119-120)
  - Double Exposure Town Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1994 Feb. 3 (Box 120)
  - Campaign for Women's Health: State Women's Health Initiative Advisory Council Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1994 Feb. 4 (Box 120)
  - 3rd Regional Meeting Mid-Atlantic Region, Baltimore, Md., 1994 Feb. 12 (Box 120)
  - Lesbian Health Roundtable, George Washington University, Washington, D.C., 1994 Feb. 27-Mar. 1 (Box 120)
  - NOA Conference Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1994 Mar. 5-6 (Box 120)
  - Women of Color Panel, Galludet University, Washington, D.C., 1994 Mar. 9 (Box 120)
  - N.C. State, North Carolina State University, Raleigh, N.C., 1994 Mar. 22 (Box 120)
  - Duke University, Duke University, Durham, N.C., 1994 Mar. 24 (Box 120)
  - Southern Alliance Building Project, 1994 Mar. 26-27 (Box 120)
  - National Council of Church Racial Justice Work Group, 1994 Mar. 27-29 (Box 121)
  - UMOJA, St. Louis, Mo., 1994 Mar. 31 (Box 121)
  - Duke University, Durham, N.C., 1994 Apr. 5 (Box 121)
  - New Jewish Democratic Council, Washington, D.C., 1994 Apr. 7 (Box 121)
  - Religious Summit May 11, 18, 25, 1994, Washington, D.C., 1994 Apr. 7 (Box 121)
  - Philadelphia Town Meeting, Philadelphia, Pa., 1994 Apr. 10 (Box 121)
  - South Carolina Pride, Columbia, S.C., 1994 Apr. 16 (Box 121)
  - SIECUS Conference, Washington, D.C., 1994 Apr. 18 (Box 121)
  - Initiative and Referendum Virginia, Richmond, Va., 1994 Apr. 23 (Box 121)
  - NGLTF Movement Building, Kansas City, Mo., 1994 Apr. 29-May 1 (Box 121)
  - National Breast Cancer Coalition Network Building, Washington, D.C., 1994 May 2 (Box 121)
  - HRCF Leadership Conference, Washington, D.C., 1994 May 7-9 (Box 121)
  - Sisters Working Together For Justice in the Workplace, Bennett College, Greensboro, N.C., 1994 May 20-22 (Box 121)
  - BGLLF Detroit Trip, Detroit, Mich., 1994 May 23-28, 3 folders (Box 122)
  - Black Pride '94, Washington, D.C., 1994 May 27-30 (Box 122)
  - Gay and Lesbian Activists Alliance, 24th Anniversary, 1994 June 1 (Box 122)
  - National Women's Music Festival, 20th Year, Bloomington, Ind., 1994 June 1-3 (Box 122)
  - NC Pride '94, Charlotte, N.C., 1994 June 3-5, 3 folders (Box 122)
  - Show Me Equality Campaign, St. Louis, Mo., 1994 June 8-9 (Box 122)
  - Atlanta Pride, Atlanta, Ga., 1994 June 12-13 (Box 122)
  - BGLLF Cleveland Trip, Cleveland, Ohio, 1994 June 18 (Box 122)
  - Gay Games IV, New York, N.Y., 1994 June 18-25 (Box 123)
  - Stonewall 25, New York, N.Y., 1994 June 26, 3 folders (Box 123)
  - Raise the Rainbow, New York, N.Y., 1994 June 26 (Box 123)
  - Los Angeles Trip, Los Angeles, Calif., 1994 July 7-10 (Box 123)
  - FOR National Convention, Louisville, Ky., 1994 July 14 (Box 123)
  - Oklahoma Pride Summit, O.S.U., Norman, Okla., 1994 July 15-17, 3 folders (Box 123)
  - Black and White Men Together, Arlington, Va., 1994 July 16-24 (Box 123)
  - Building Bridges, Keysville, Ga., 1994 July 22-24 (Box 124)
  - Toledo, Ohio, 1994 Aug. 10-14, 2 folders (Box 124)
  - Lansing, Mich., 1994 Aug. 15-21 (Box 124)
  - National Organizers Alliance Conference, Evergreen State College, Olympia, Wash., 1994 Aug. 25-28 (Box 124)
  - NET TV Show, Washington, D.C., 1994 Sept. 9 (Box 124)
  - Sister Space, Poconos, Pa., 1994 Sept. 10 (Box 124)
  - Unity Expo, Los Angeles, Calif., 1994 Sept. 10-11 (Box 124)
  - National Congress on State of HIV/AIDS in POC Communities, Washington, D.C., 1994 Sept. 15-18 (Box 124)
  - Philadelphia Unity Meeting, Philadelphia, Pa., 1994 Sept. 23 (Box 124)
  - Opening Doors Conference, Chapel Hill, N.C., 1994 Oct. 1 (Box 124)
  - St. Louis Pride, St. Louis, Mo., 1994 Oct. 2 (Box 124)
  - National Coming Out Day, Omaha, Neb., 1994 Oct. 7-8 (Box 124)
  - D.C. Coalition of Black Lesbians, Gay Men, and Bisexuals, Annual Meeting, Howard University, Washington, D.C., 1994 Oct. 7-9 (Box 125)
  - National Coming Out Day, 1994 Oct. 11 (Box 125)
  - Reel Affirmations, Washington, D.C., 1994 Oct. 13-23 (Box 125)
  - Phil Donahue, New York, N.Y., 1994 Oct. 19 (Box 125)
  - HIV/Lavendar Law Conference Diversity Panel, Portland, Or., 1994 Oct. 21-23, 2 folders (Box 125)
  - Hawaii Marriage LAMBDA, NYC, New York, N.Y., 1994 Oct. 28 (Box 125)
  - Unity Conference of Chicago Black Lesbians and Gays, Chicago, Ill., 1994 Nov. 5 (Box 125)
  - Creating Change, Dallas, Tex., 1994 Nov. 9-13, 4 folders (Box 125)
  - Howard University, Washington, D.C., 1994 Nov. 18 (Box 125)
  - Blue Mountain Retreat, 1994 Nov. 16-20 (Box 126)
  - New Women's Movement National Planning Process, Chicago, Ill., 1994 Nov. 18-20 (Box 126)
  - Integrity Southeastern Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1994 Dec. 10 (Box 126)
  - Kwanzaa, 1994 (Box 126)
  - Sabbatical, Detroit, Mich., 1995 (Box 126)
  - National Rainbow Coalition Conference, Washington, D.C., 1995 Jan. 5-7 (Box 126)
  - Ladyslipper Board Meeting, Durham, N.C., 1995 Jan. 18 (Box 126)
  - National Rainbow Coalition Follow-Up Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1995 Jan. 23 (Box 126)
  - Passages Conference, University of Maryland, College Park, Md., 1995 Feb. 11 (Box 126)
  - Promoting Our Traditional Values: Responding to the Religions Right, Workshop Evaluations (Box 126)
  - Unitarian Universalists for L/G/B/T Concerns: Interweave, Raleigh, N.C., 1995 Feb. 17-19 (Box 126)
  - LAMBDA Association of Fayetteville, Fayetteville, N.C., 1995 Feb. 25 (Box 126)
  - Princeton University, Princeton, N.J., 1995 Mar. 23-24 (Box 126)
  - Fayetteville LAMBDA Association, Fayetteville, N.C., 1995 Mar. 26 (Box 126)
  - Human Rights Week, North Carolina State University, Raleigh, N.C., 1995 Mar. 27-28 (Box 126)
  - National Day of Campus Action, 1995 Mar. 29 (Box 126)
  - Detroit, Mich., 1995 Mar. 31 (Box 126)
  - Texas March, Austin, Tex., 1995 Apr. 2 (Box 126)
  - South Carolina Gay and Lesbian Pride Week, Columbia, S.C., 1995 Apr. 3-9, 2 folders (Box 126)
  - NOW Rally for Women's Lives, Washington, D.C., 1995 Apr. 9 (Box 103)
  - Cleveland, Ohio, 1995 Apr. 14-18 (Box 127)
  - Philadelphia Lesbian and Gay Task Force, Philadelphia, Pa., 1995 Apr. 22-25, 2 folders (Box 127)
  - National Interfaith Network Strategy Conference, Eugene, Or., 1995 Apr. 27-May 1 (Box 127)
  - Claiming the Spirit: Uniting Faith, Rights, and Sexuality, Denver, Colo., 1995 May 4-6, 2 folders (Box 127)
  - Ohio Trip, 1995 May 15-20, 2 folders (Box 127-128)
  - Gay Youth Pride March and Rally, Boston, Mass., 1995 May 20 (Box 128)
  - National Rainbow Coalition Walk For Justice, Atlanta, Ga., 1995 May 21-23 (Box 128)
  - National Rainbow Coalition National Conference, Atlanta, Ga., 1995 May 25-27, 2 folders (Box 128)
  - Black Lesbian and Gay Pride Weekend, Washington, D.C., 1995 May 26-28, 2 folders (Box 128)
  - Grassroots Now! Retreat, Rehoboth Beach, Del., 1995 June 2-5, 2 folders (Box 128)
  - Heartland Project Board Meeting, Rehoboth Beach, Del., 1995 June 3 (Box 128)
  - Management of Community Develepment Institute, Tufts University, Meford, Mass., 1995 June 3-10 (Box 128)
  - North Carolina Pride, Durham, N.C., 1995 June 9-11, 2 folders (Box 128)
  - Cincinnati Pride Week, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1995 June 14-17 (Box 128)
  - Nashville, Tenn., 1995 June 17-18 (Box 129)
  - National Women's Studies Association, Norman, Okla., 1995 June 21-25 (Box 129)
  - Atlanta Pride, Atlanta, Ga., 1995 June 23-25 (Box 129)
  - Little Rock, Ark., 1995 June 25 (Box 129)
  - NABWMT Crystal Celebration, Key West, Fla., 1995 July 15-22, 2 folders (Box 129)
  - National Committee for Independent Polticial Actions, Independent Politics Summit, 1995 Aug. 18-20, 2 folders (Box 129)
  - Rhythm Fest, S.C., 1995 Aug. 31-Sept. 4 (Box 129)
  - D.C. Coalition of Black Lesbians, Gay Men, and Bisexuals Conference, Washington, D.C., 1995 Sept. 15-16, 2 folders (Box 130)
  - Black Colleges and the 104th Congress, Washington, D.C., 1995 Sept. 19-23 (Box 130)
  - Congressional Black Cacus Foundation 25th Annual Legislative Conference, Washington, D.C., 1995 Sept. 21-23, 3 folders (Box 130)
  - Downeast Pride, Greenville, N.C., 1995 Sept. 22-23 (Box 130)
  - PFLAG 14th National Conference, Indianapolis, Ind., 1995 Sept. 29-Oct. 1 (Box 130)
  - POC Summit, 1995 Oct. 5-9 (Box 130)
  - Pre-Colorado Decision, 1995 Oct. 9 (Box 130)
  - Virginia Tech National Coming Out Day, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Va., 1995 Oct. 11 (Box 131)
  - OutCharlotte, Charlotte, N.C., 1995 Oct. 11-15, 3 folders (Box 131)
  - SEAC Conference, UNC-Chapel Hill, Chapel Hill, N.C., 1995 Oct. 13-15 (Box 131)
  - Million Man March, Washington, D.C., 1995 Oct. 16 (Box 131)
  - Unleash the Power, Henderson, Ky., 1995 Oct. 13-14 (Box 131)
  - Peace with Justice Week, Henderson, Ky., 1995 Oct. 15-18 (Box 131)
  - 2nd Annual WOC in Workplace, Louisville, Ky., 1995 Oct. 26-29 (Box 131)
  - 16th Anniversary Dinner Closer, Asheville, N.C., 1995 Nov. 7 (Box 131)
  - Creating Change 1995, Detriot, Mich., 1995 Nov. 8-12, 3 folders (Box 131)
  - PFAW National Network Agenda, 1995 Nov. 13 (Box 131)
  - Barry Yeoman, Durham, N.C., 1995 Nov. 16 (Box 132)
  - Women's Leadership and Grassroots Activisim, Duke University, Durham, N.C., 1995 Nov. 28-29 (Box 132)
  - Triangle Meeting, Durham, N.C., 1995 Dec. 7 (Box 132)
  - 6th Grassroots Leadership Conference, Fairfield County, S.C., 1995 Dec. 8-10 (Box 132)
  - Pride of the Southeast, Atlanta, Ga., 1996 Jan. 13-14 (Box 132)
  - Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Issues: Multicultural Community Building, Needs, Challenges, and Opportunities, Wayne State University, Detroit, Mich., 1996 Feb. 9, 2 folders (Box 132)
  - NC HRCF Dinner, Greensboro, N.C., 1996 Feb. 10 (Box 132)
  - Ladyslipper Board Meeting, 1996 Feb. 14 (Box 132)
  - National Black Lesbian and Gay Conference, Dallas, Tex., 1996 Feb. 15-19, 2 folders (Box 132)
  - DNC Meeting, 1996 Feb. 16-18 (Box 132)
  - Chicago Unity '96, Chicago, Ill., 1996 Feb. 23-25 (Box 133)
  - DNC Training Academy, Decatur, Ga., 1996 Feb. 25-Mar. 1 (Box 133)
  - Leather Weekend, Wilmington, N.C., 1996 Mar. 2-3 (Box 133)
  - Brown University Pride, Brown University, Providence, R.I., 1996 Mar. 18 (Box 133)
  - NOW Southeast Regional Conference, Raleigh, N.C., 1996 Mar. 29-31, 3 folders (Box 133)
  - 6th Annual National Queer Coalition's LGBT Graduate Students, Miami University, Oxford, Ohio, 1996 Apr. 4-7 (Box 133)
  - Lesbigay Awareness Week, University of Central Florida, Orlando, Fla., 1996 Apr. 8-12 (Box 133)
  - S.U.N. Conference, Stetson University, DeLand, Fla., 1996 Apr. [12-15?] (Box 133)
  - University of Central Florida/Stetson University, Orlando, Fla., 1996 Apr. 13-16, 2 folders (Box 133)
  - Summit on Ethics and Meaning, Washington, D.C., 1996 Apr. 14-16 (Box 133)
  - Women's Funding National Network Conference, Atlanta, Ga., 1996 Apr. 17-21, 2 folders (Box 134)
  - South Carolina Gay and Lesbian Pride Rally, 1996 Apr. 26-28, 2 folders (Box 134)
  - Bisexual, Gay, and Lesbian Awareness Days, Stanford University, Palo Alto, Calif., 1996 Apr. 29, 2 folders (Box 134)
  - Philadelphia Pride Fest '96 and National Lesbian and Gay Democrats Meeting, Philadelphia, Pa., 1996 May 3-5, 2 folders (Box 134)
  - Black Lesbian and Gay Pride Weekend, Washington, D.C., 1996 May 24-27 (Box 134)
  - Justice, Inc., Indianapolis, Ind., 1996 June 5 (Box 134)
  - National Women's Music Festival '96, Bloomington, Ind., 1996 June 5-7, 2 folders (Box 134)
  - NC Pride 1996, Winston-Salem, N.C., 1996 June 7-9, 3 folders (Box 134)
  - Pride Week '96, Nashville, Tenn., 1996 June 13 (Box 134)
  - NC State Democratic Party, Durham, N.C., 1996 June 15 (Box 134)
  - "How Democracy Works", Atlanta, Ga., 1996 June 17 (Box 135)
  - NOW National Conference, Las Vegas, Nev., 1996 June 29 (Box 103)
  - SF Pride, San Francisco, Calif., 1996 June 30 (Box 135)
  - Strategy Source, San Francisco, Calif., 1996 July 1 (Box 135)
  - Tampa Pride Fest '96, Tampa, Fla., 1996 July 6 (Box 135)
  - Gayla Tampa Pride, Tampa, Fla., 1996 July 7-9 (Box 135)
  - The Economy and Lesbigaytrans Liberation, Asheville, N.C., 1996 July 10 (Box 135)
  - FSC 15th Anniversary, Durham, N.C., 1996 July 13, 3 folders (Box 135)
  - NABWMT National Conference, Cleveland, Ohio, 1996 July 24-27 (Box 135)
  - UUA Mountain Retreat, 1996 Aug. 6-10 (Box 135)
  - APA Conference, Toronto, Canada, 1996 Aug. 10-11, 2 folders (Box 135)
  - Democratic National Convention, Chicago, Ill., 1996 Aug. 25-29, 4 folders (Box 136)
  - Downeast Pride, Greenville, N.C., 1996 Sept. 13-14 (Box 136)
  - NC NOW Conference, 1996 Sept. 21 (Box 136)
  - HBCU Day, North Carolina Central University, Durham, N.C., 1996 Sept. 23 (Box 136)
  - Bar Party, Ann Arbor, Mich., 1996 Sept. 27 (Box 136)
  - Defeat Helms Week, Duke University, Durham, N.C., 1996 Sept. 30-Oct. 4 (Box 136)
  - Highlander Retreat, New Market, Tenn., 1996 Oct. 4-6 (Box 136)
  - UCLA National Coming Out Day, Los Angeles, Calif., 1996 Oct. 7-8 (Box 136)
  - Denver National Coming Out Day, Denver, Colo., 1996 Oct. 9-11 (Box 137)
  - National Coming Out Day, 1996 Oct. 11 (Box 137)
  - AIDS Quilt, Washington, D.C., 1996 Oct. 11-13 (Box 137)
  - PFLAG 15th National Conference, Washington, D.C., 1996 Oct. 11-14, 2 folders (Box 137)
  - SF Fundraiser, San Francisco, Calif., 1996 Oct. 15 (Box 137)
  - OutCharlotte '96, Charlotte, N.C., 1996 Oct. 16-20, 3 folders (Box 137)
  - Pride, Inc., Myrtle Beach, S.C., 1996 Oct. 19-20 (Box 137)
  - NGLTF Creating Change '96, Alexandria, Va., 1996 Nov. 6-10 (Box 137)
  - Prep 10th Gala, St. Louis, Mo., 1996 Nov. 15 (Box 137)
  - SE MCC Convention, Charlotte, N.C., 1996 Nov. 16 (Box 137)
  - No Easy Walk: Lessons and Legacies from the North Carolina Fund Conference, Durham, N.C., 1996 Dec. 13-14 (Box 137)
  - University of Iowa, Iowa City, Iowa, 1997 Jan. 22-26 (Box 137)
  - BGLLF 10th Anniversary Conference, Long Beach, Calif., 1997 Feb. 13-17 (Box 137)
  - Old Dominion University, Old Dominion University, Norfolk, Va., 1997 Mar. 5 (Box 138)
  - Interfaith Conference on Promise Keepers, Washington, D.C., 1997 Mar. 10-11 (Box 138)
  - NBLGLF Meetings: Keith-Staff-Terrance, 1997 Mar. 25 (Box 138)
  - GLAAD 8th Annual Media Awards, 1997 Mar. 26 (Box 138)
  - FSJ-Mark, Michael, 1997 Mar. 26 (Box 138)
  - Women at the Beach, Holden Beach, N.C., 1997 Mar. 27-28 (Box 138)
  - Hoyle Martin, 1997 Apr. 1-4 (Box 138)
  - Come Together Kentucky, Louisville, Ky., 1997 Apr. 4-6, 2 folders (Box 138)
  - KFA, Louisville, Ky., 1997 Apr. 4-8 (Box 138)
  - Church Burnings, Columbia, S.C., 1997 Apr. 11-13 (Box 138)
  - Pact, 1997 Apr. 15-16 (Box 138)
  - South Carolina Pride, Greenville, S.C., 1997 Apr. 18-20 (Box 138)
  - Unity and Harmony 2000, Reynolds Coliseum, North Carolina State University, Raleigh, N.C., 1997 Apr. 24, 2 folders (Box 139)
  - National Youth Advocacy Coalition First Annual Summit, Washington, D.C., 1997 Apr. 26-28, 2 folders (Box 139)
  - University of Maryland Meetings, University of Maryland, College Park, Md., 1997 Apr. 29 (Box 139)
  - PK Steering Committee, Brooklyn, N.Y., 1997 Apr. 30, 3 folders (Box 139)
  - Baltimore Town Meeting, Baltimore, Md., 1997 May 1, 2 folders (Box 139)
  - Denver Trip, Co., 1997 May 8-11 (Box 139)
  - Congress on Racial Reconciliation, Baltimore, Md., 1997 May 10 (Box 139)
  - Baltimore Meeting: Solidarity Rally, Baltimore, Md., 1997 May 14 (Box 139)
  - 7th Annual D.C. Black Pride, Washington, D.C., 1997 May 22-26, 2 folders (Box 140)
  - National Women's Music Festival '97, Bloomington, Ind., 1997 May 29-June 1 (Box 140)
  - Reach OUT Reach, Raleigh, N.C., 1997 June 5-7 (Box 140)
  - Activist Training, UNC-Chapel Hill, Chapel Hill, N.C., 1997 June 6 (Box 140)
  - NC Pride '97, Carborro-Chapel Hill, N.C., 1997 June 6-8, 3 folders (Box 140)
  - Washington, D.C., 1997 June 11-14 (Box 140)
  - National Black Religious Summit on Sexuality, Breaking the Silence, Washington, D.C., 1997 June 12-13 (Box 140)
  - People for the American Way, National Network Meeting, 1997 June 26 (Box 141)
  - St. Louis Pride '97, St. Louis, Mo., 1997 June 29 (Box 141)
  - All God's Children, St. Louis, Mo., 1997 June 30 (Box 141)
  - RCRC Follow Up Meeting, 1997 July 1 (Box 141)
  - NOW National Conference, Memphis, Tenn., 1997 July 4-6 (Box 103)
  - Washington, D.C. Trip, Washington, D.C., 1997 July 7-9 (Box 141)
  - NABWMT Convention '97, Charlotte, N.C., 1997 July 10-12 (Box 141)
  - POC LGBT Meeting, Charlotte, N.C., 1997 July 12 (Box 141)
  - NLPAC Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1997 July 15 (Box 141)
  - National Association of Black Journalists, Chicago, Ill., 1997 July 15-20, 2 folders (Box 141-142)
  - Dwayne S. Brown Foundation, William Beale Meeting, 1997 July 16 (Box 142)
  - Voices of Faith '97, Denver, Colo., 1997 July 23-29 (Box 142)
  - C/L Film Festival, Durham, N.C., 1997 Aug. 2 (Box 142)
  - WRL Training, 1997 Aug. 12 (Box 142)
  - Cleveland Black Pride, Cleveland, Ohio, 1997 Aug. 16-17 (Box 142)
  - Gill Foundation TA Retreat, 1997 Aug. 20-22 (Box 142)
  - Lavendar Languages and Linguistics, Washington, D.C., 1997 Sept. 19-21 (Box 143)
  - CWA Training, 1997 Sept. 22 (Box 143)
  - NC NOW Conference, Boone, N.C., 1997 Sept. 27 (Box 143)
  - NWC 11th Conference, Colorado Springs, Colo., 1997 Sept. 27-28 (Box 143)
  - NET, Washington, D.C., 1997 Oct. 2 (Box 143)
  - OutCharlotte '97, Charlotte, N.C., 1997 Oct. 11 (Box 143)
  - PWJW '97, Henderson, Ky., 1997 Oct. 18 (Box 143)
  - Public Welfare Foundation, Washington, D.C., 1997 Oct. 23-24 (Box 143)
  - GLAAD, 1997 Oct. 29 (Box 143)
  - 97 SRC/AWP Conference, Wilmington, N.C., 1997 Nov. 1-2 (Box 143)
  - Union Institute Women Organizers, Chicago, Ill., 1997 Nov. 6-9 (Box 143)
  - Creating Change '97, San Francisco, Calif., 1997 Nov. 11-16, 2 folders (Box 143-144)
  - Political Research Associates (PRA), 1997 Dec. 3-4 (Box 144)
  - California Prop 209 Meeting, 1997 Dec. 4, 2 folders (Box 144)
  - PFAW Network Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1998 Jan. 8 (Box 144)
  - Oakland, Calif., 1998 Jan. 9-12 (Box 144)
  - NC NOW Rally Roe v. Wade, Raleigh, N.C., 1998 Jan. 12 (Box 144)
  - Ladyslipper Board Meeting, 1998 Jan. 14 (Box 144)
  - NC NOW PAC Meeting, Raleigh, N.C., 1998 Jan. 15 (Box 144)
  - Mary Williams College, 1998 Jan. 22 (Box 144)
  - EPF Meeting, Charlotte, N.C., 1998 Jan. 29 (Box 144)
  - Equal Partners in Faith, 1998 Feb. 5-6 (Box 144)